<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Eldoria]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Eldoria</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:33:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:33:07 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[JP Player Sheet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Character NameJP's CharacterClassWizardLevel5RaceElfStrength8+0Dexterity14+0Constitution12+0Intelligence18+0Wisdom13+0Charisma10+0Proficiency Bonus+2Initiative+0Armor Class12Speed30 ftStrength+0Dexterity+0Constitution+0Intelligence+0Wisdom+0Charisma+0Acrobatics (Dex)+0Animal Handling (Wis)+0Arcana (Int)+0Athletics (Str)+0Deception (Cha)+0History (Int)+0Insight (Wis)+0Intimidation (Cha)+0Investigation (Int)+0Medicine (Wis)+0Nature (Int)+0Perception (Wis)+0Performance (Cha)+0Persuasion (Cha)+0Religion (Int)+0Sleight of Hand (Dex)+0Stealth (Dex)+0Survival (Wis)+0 Longsword none weapon, martial weapon, melee weapon Source: PHB'14 (pg. 149) Damage: 1d8 slashing Properties: versatile (1d10) Weight: 3 lb. Value: 15 gp Versatile. This weapon can be used with one or two hands. A damage value in parentheses appears with the property—the damage when the weapon is used with two hands to make a melee attack. Bag of Holding uncommon wondrous item Source: DMG'14 (pg. 153) Weight: 15 lb. Value: 100 gp This bag has an interior space considerably larger than its outside dimensions, roughly 2 feet in diameter at the mouth and 4 feet deep. The bag can hold up to 500 pounds, not exceeding a volume of 64 cubic feet. The bag weighs 15 pounds, regardless of its contents. Retrieving an item from the bag requires an action.If the bag is overloaded, pierced, or torn, it ruptures and is destroyed, and its contents are scattered in the Astral Plane. If the bag is turned inside out, its contents spill forth, unharmed, but the bag must be put right before it can be used again. Breathing creatures inside the bag can survive up to a number of minutes equal to 10 divided by the number of creatures (minimum 1 minute), after which time they begin to suffocate.Placing a bag of holding inside an extradimensional space created by a Heward's handy haversack, portable hole, or similar item instantly destroys both items and opens a gate to the Astral Plane. The gate originates where the one item was placed inside the other. Any creature within 10 feet of the gate is sucked through it to a random location on the Astral Plane. The gate then closes. The gate is one-way only and can't be reopened. Ring of Protection rare ring Source: DMG'14 (pg. 191) Attunement: requires attunement Value: 13000 gp You gain a +1 bonus to AC and saving throws while wearing this ring. ]]></description><link>jp-player-sheet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PlayerNotes/Players/JP Player Sheet.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>